{
    "title": "Number Systems",
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionText": "If the binary number 110101001100 is converted to octal, how many digits will the octal number contain?",
            "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6", "not enough information"],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "questionText": "In the hexadecimal system, how many numbers are there between 58 and 62 (not including 58 and 62)?",
            "choices": ["3", "6", "9", "12", "not enough information"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "In the octal number system, 77 + 1 = ?",
            "choices": ["78", "80", "100", "777", "none of the above"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "If the left-most digit of a hexadecimal number is 1, and all of the other digits are 0, then number must be:",
            "choices": [
                "a power of 16",
                "a power of 8",
                "a power of 2",
                "all of the above",
                "none of the above"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionText": "16 ^ 2222 = ",
            "choices": [
                "2 ^ 8888",
                "8 ^ 4444",
                "10 ^ 6666",
                "not enough information"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "What is the decimal equivalent of the largest seven-digit binary number?",
            "choices": [
                "255",
                "256",
                "512",
                "1000000",
                "not enough information"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following is a valid number in a base-6 system?",
            "choices": [
                "45",
                "55",
                "65",
                "a and b",
                "b and c",
                "all of the above"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "questionText": "A bus can hold 24 passengers, and a car can hold 3 passengers. If every bus used must be full, what is the minimum number of vehicles needed to transport 100 people?",
            "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7", "not enough information"],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Which of the following statements is true?",
            "choices": [
                "Every power of 8 is a power of 2",
                "Every power of 8 is a power of 16",
                "Every power of 2 is a power of 8",
                "Every power of 16 is a power of 8."
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "questionText": "Let n be an integer greater than 1. Which of the following numbers is greater than 0?",
            "choices": [
                "n * n % n / n",
                "n * n / n % n",
                "n / n % n * n",
                "n / n * n % n",
                "n % n * n / n",
                "n % n / n * n"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        }
    ]
}
